let questions15 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "affair",
      answer: "A. Angelegenheit",
      options: [
        "A. Angelegenheit",
        "B. Feier",
        "C. Reise",
        "D. Aufgabe"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "assembly",
      answer: "C. Versammlung",
      options: [
        "A. Organisation",
        "B. Schule",
        "C. Versammlung",
        "D. Gruppe"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "to bless",
      answer: "D. segnen",
      options: [
        "A. bitten",
        "B. schützen",
        "C. danken",
        "D. segnen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "cereal",
      answer: "B. Müsli",
      options: [
        "A. Brot",
        "B. Müsli",
        "C. Butter",
        "D. Obst"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "cheerful",
      answer: "C. fröhlich",
      options: [
        "A. müde",
        "B. nervös",
        "C. fröhlich",
        "D. böse"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "diameter",
      answer: "A. Durchmesser",
      options: [
        "A. Durchmesser",
        "B. Radius",
        "C. Fläche",
        "D. Volumen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "to exploit",
      answer: "B. ausnutzen",
      options: [
        "A. reparieren",
        "B. ausnutzen",
        "C. verteilen",
        "D. ignorieren"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "famine",
      answer: "D. Hungersnot",
      options: [
        "A. Überschwemmung",
        "B. Erdbeben",
        "C. Dürre",
        "D. Hungersnot"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "harvest",
      answer: "C. Ernte",
      options: [
        "A. Regen",
        "B. Getreide",
        "C. Ernte",
        "D. Saat"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "merry",
      answer: "B. glücklich",
      options: [
        "A. traurig",
        "B. glücklich",
        "C. wütend",
        "D. erschöpft"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "nut",
      answer: "D. Nuss",
      options: [
        "A. Apfel",
        "B. Brot",
        "C. Frucht",
        "D. Nuss"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "to pardon",
      answer: "C. entschuldigen",
      options: [
        "A. vergessen",
        "B. erklären",
        "C. entschuldigen",
        "D. erinnern"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "pharaoh",
      answer: "A. Pharao",
      options: [
        "A. Pharao",
        "B. Kaiser",
        "C. König",
        "D. Prinz"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "ripe",
      answer: "B. reif",
      options: [
        "A. sauer",
        "B. reif",
        "C. hart",
        "D. roh"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "to roast",
      answer: "D. rösten",
      options: [
        "A. kochen",
        "B. backen",
        "C. braten",
        "D. rösten"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "routine",
      answer: "C. Routine",
      options: [
        "A. Übung",
        "B. Plan",
        "C. Routine",
        "D. Methode"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "scheme",
      answer: "B. Schema",
      options: [
        "A. Karte",
        "B. Schema",
        "C. Plan",
        "D. Idee"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "slim",
      answer: "A. schlank",
      options: [
        "A. schlank",
        "B. dick",
        "C. groß",
        "D. kurz"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "stove",
      answer: "D. Herd",
      options: [
        "A. Ofen",
        "B. Mikrowelle",
        "C. Kühlschrank",
        "D. Herd"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "theft",
      answer: "A. Diebstahl",
      options: [
        "A. Diebstahl",
        "B. Betrug",
        "C. Raub",
        "D. Einbruch"
      ]
    }
  ];
  
  export default questions15;
  